gulfy.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Gulfy

**Your Privacy Rights**

Gulfy collects information about you and uses this information to help you connect with employers and job seekers and to provide other services to you. This policy describes how your information is collected and used and your choices with respect to your personal information.

**Scope of this Policy**

This policy applies to information we collect or use on sites and applications owned or controlled by Gulfy or its affiliated companies. Gulfy is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of ad networks and other websites, third parties with whom we work to provide you personalized services, or those who access your information on our sites or applications.

**Information We Collect**

We collect information about you when you use Gulfy. We collect information directly from you such as your contact information, resume, and profile information. We only collect data that is necessary to facilitate recruitment in the GCC, for example, taking into consideration government restrictions on Visa Allocations by Nationality or gender. We also collect information about you automatically such as how you use and interact with Gulfy, your demographic information, and information about your computer or mobile device using standard analytics tools such as Google Analytics.

You will have the opportunity to claim, change the visibility setting of, or remove the information.

**How We Use Information**

We use the information we collect about you to deliver the products and services we offer, respond to you, and operate and improve our sites and applications. Our services include showing you personalized content and jobs. We may use your information to contact you about Gulfy updates, conduct surveys, or to provide informational and service-related communications, including important security updates.

Information you share in public areas of Gulfy or make visible in the resume and profile database may be accessed, used, and stored by others around the world. We strive to provide a safe environment by attempting to limit access to our database to legitimate users, but we cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will not gain access. We also cannot control how authorized users store or transfer information you give to us, so you should not post sensitive information to Gulfy. Only companies with a registered business domain will be able to view your contact details unless you activate your public Gulfy profile. This profile can be switched on and off via your control panel.

**How We Share Information**

We do not share contact information with third parties other than companies seeking employees that make sure of the website and App services and features. We disclose information where legally required by law. We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires any or all of Gulfy in the future or are part of Gulfy subsidiaries. 

**How We Store Information**

We store your information to make your interaction with Gulfy more efficient, practical, and relevant. You may access, review, correct, update, or delete your resume or profile any time by signing in to your account. When you delete your personal information, we will retain logs and non-personal information about your activity on Gulfy. We will also retain an archival copy of your information which is not accessible by you or third parties on the Internet. If your personal information was previously accessed by others using Gulfy, we are unable to delete the information from their systems. All data is stored with Cloud Servers that offer one of the highest levels of security available online, your data security is critical to us and we strive to utlize the best tools available for this purpose.

**Other Information**

Gulfy is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We use cookies to help personalize and maximize your online experience on Gulfy.

**Mobile Applications**

Gulfy offers several mobile applications, including the Gulfy App for both Apple and Android. Gulfy collects and uses information in the same way for the applications as the website. 

**Contact Information**

You may contact us online for questions or concerns about our privacy practices at [support@gulfy.com](mailto:support@gulfy.com). You may also write to us at:

**Privacy Office**

Gulfy.com

Last Updated: 28th January 2018
